Okay, what's the next thing we need to characterize about our metrics in
接下来 为了对实验进行分析
order to analyze the experiment?
我们需要了解指标的什么方面？
>> Well, the next thing we need to talk about is variability.
我们接下来要讨论差异性
Up until now, we've talked sort of about developing intuition for the metric,
到目前为止 我们已经讨论了就指标培养直觉
about sensitivity, and robustness.
敏感性以及稳健性
But now, we're going to need a really more rigorous statistical
现在 我们需要从统计学角度对差异性给出更严谨的定义
definition of variability, so that we can use it in lesson four to look at
以便在第四课中使用它来确定实验规模
sizing the experiment, and in lesson five to actually analyze the confidence
并在第五课中根据它分析置信区间
intervals, and draw conclusions.
和得出结论
We also want to check that the practical significance level we're interested in,
我们还需要检查我们感兴趣的实际显著性水平
is really realistic for our metric.
对于指标而言是否真的有实际意义
If we have a metric that varies a lot under normal circumstances, that may not
如果指标在正常情况下即存在很大变动
really work for us in practice, because the practical significance level
那么它在实践中就没什么用 因为我们感兴趣的实际显著性
we're interested in, just may not be feasible with this metric.
对于这一指标可能不切实际
>> Okay, so, how would we figure that out?
如何才能弄清楚这一点？
>> Well, in lesson one we did a simple example
我们在第一课中讨论了一个有关点击概率的简单例子
of our click-through probability, where we looked at user data which was
当时我们分析了用户数据
whether the user clicked on a specific link or not.
也就是用户有没有点击某个特定链接
And our summary statistic was the overall click-through probability.
我们得出总的统计结果就是总体点击概率
In that case, we were able to do an analytic, or a theoretical
在那个例子中 我们对预期总体概率的方差
computation of the variance that we expected from our overall probability.
进行了分析计算 也就是理论计算
Now, for other types of metrics, the same thing works.
这个计算方法也适用于其他类型的指标
For example, if you have nice normal data,
例如 如果你要分析一些很标准的数据
like demographic data, you have counts or probabilities, then usually,
比如人口统计数据 其中有计数或者概率数据
you can do the, the confidence interval, theoretically.
那么你通常可以采用理论计算来得出置信区间
But in some other cases, you may actually have to do this another way.
但在其他案例中 你可能需要采用另一种方法
So, if you're using something like a count or a probability,
所以 如果使用计数或概率
then you're only really dealing with the variability of a single measurement, or
那你就只能计算一种指标的差异性
of a constrained one, in the case of probability.
或者是受限指标的差异性 如果使用概率的话
If you move on to using ratios or percentiles, like the 90th percentile,
如果使用比例或百分比 例如 90%
or if your data, like our latency data, is pretty lumpy,
或者如果数据量很大 例如我们的延迟数据
then you probably want to actually compute the variability empirically,
那你可能得选择根据经验来计算差异性
which we'll talk about a bit more in, in a moment.
稍后我们来详细讨论这个问题